(Raj:)that NASA's been
working on?
Yeah.
(Raj:)Well, they're looking
to include a message from Earth
(Raj:)in case one of them
is encountered by alien life.
LEONARD: Oh.
(Leonard:)When I encountered alien life,
I-I discovered
(Leonard:)that the key thing
was not to sit in its spot.
(Sheldon:)All right, you can't breathe
our air without an inhaler,
(Sheldon:)he's allergic
to Earth nuts,
(Sheldon:)but I'm the alien.
KOOTHRAPPALI:
Anyway,
(Raj:)I'm among a handful
of scientists
(Raj:)that have been asked to submit
a design proposal
(Raj:)for the message
and its delivery system.
(Sheldon:)Excellent.
Congratulations.
Good for you.
(Raj:)And I was wondering
if any of you guys
(Raj:)would like
to help me do it.
(Leonard:)Are you kidding? Yes.
What did you have in mind?
(Sheldon:)I'll tell you exactly what you
should do: avoid the presumption
(Sheldon:)of the Terran sensory
input paradigm.
WOLOWITZ: Yeah, absolutely.
(Howard:)You need a device capable
of delivering information
(Howard:)across a wide range
of perceptual modalities.
(Sheldon:)Any intelligent organism
would at the very least need
(Sheldon:)the ability to locate the
position of objects in space.
(Sheldon:)So the ideal interstellar
lingua franca would be haptic.
(Howard:)Ooh, how about a 3-D
tactile communicator rigged
(Howard:)for cross-sensory transposition?
(Raj:)Exactly what I expected.
(Raj:)Two people
forcing their ideas on me
(Raj:)and only one gentleman
who could be bothered
(Raj:)to ask me what my thoughts were.
(Raj:)You two are out.
Congratulations, Leonard,
(Raj:)you're on the team.
(Leonard:)My mommy raised a gentleman.